<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="hello">Hello World, AndroidDashboardDesignActivity!</string>
    <string name="app_name">AndroidDashboardDesign</string>
    <string name="quants">Quantitative</string>
    <string name="language">Language</string>
    <string name="verbal">Verbal And Logical</string>
    <string name="compfun">Computer Fundamentals</string>
    <string name="interview">Interview</string>
    <string name="tutorial">Tutorial</string>
    <string name="puzzles">Brain Teasers</string>
    <string name="allinone">All In One</string>
    <string name="c">C</string>
    <string name="cpp">C++</string>
    <string name="java">Java</string>
    <string name="html">HTML</string>
    <string name="os">Operating System</string>
    <string name="dbms">Database Management System </string>
    <string name="dsa">Data Structures</string>
    <string name="q1">Numbers And Simplification</string>
    <string name="q2">Square Root And Cube Root</string>
    <string name="q4">Problem on Numbers And Ages</string>
    <string name="q5">Percentage</string>
    <string name="q6">Profit And Loss</string>
    <string name="q7">Ratio And Proportion</string>
    <string name="q8">Partnership</string>
    <string name="q10">Time And Work And Distance</string>
    <string name="q11">Problem On Trains,Boats And Streams</string>
    <string name="q12">Simple Interest And Compound Interest</string>
    <string name="q13">Area And Volume</string>
    <string name="q15">Stocks And Shares</string>
    <string name="q16">Permutation And Combination</string>
    <string name="q17">Probablity</string>
    <string name="c1">Declaration And Initialization</string>
    <string name="c2">Contol Instructions</string>
    <string name="c3">Exprssions</string>
    <string name="c4">Floationg Point</string>
    <string name="c5">Functions</string>
    <string name="c6">C Preprocessor</string>
    <string name="c7">Pointers</string>
    <string name="c8">Arrays And Strings</string>
    <string name="c9">Structures,Unions,Enums </string>
    <string name="c10">Input Output</string>
    <string name="c11">Command Line Arguments</string>
    <string name="c12">Bitwise Operator</string>
    <string name="c13">Typedef,Const,Memory Allocation</string>
    <string name="c14">VarArgs,Complicated Declarations</string>
    <string name="cpp1">OOP Concepts </string>
    <string name="cpp2">Constructors And Destructors </string>
    <string name="cpp3">Pointers, Arrays, Constants, Structures </string>
    <string name="cpp4">Functions And Macros </string>
    <string name="cpp5">Operator And Overloading</string>
    <string name="cpp6">Derived Classes, templates and Exception Handling</string>
    <string name="cpp7"> Strings and Streams</string>
    <string name="j1">Basics,Control Statements,Operators </string>
    <string name="j2">Classes And Object </string>
    <string name="j3">Input And Output,Arrays,Strings</string>
    <string name="j4">Inheritance,Abstract Classes,Interfaces,Packeges</string>
    <string name="j5">Excception Handling And Assertions</string>
    <string name="j6">Enumerators And Nested Classes</string>
    <string name="j7">Files An Serialization</string>
    <string name="j8"> Threads</string>
    <string name="j9">Collections And Generics</string>
    <string name="j10">Formatters</string>
    <string name="v1">Analogy </string>
    <string name="v2">Classification</string>
    <string name="v3">Series Complition</string>
    <string name="v4">Coding And Decoding</string>
    <string name="v5">Blood Relations</string>
    <string name="v6">Logical Sequence And Words</string>
    <string name="v7">Decision Making</string>
    <string name="v8">Data Suffiiency</string>
    <string name="v9">Cause And Effects</string>
    <string name="head">Aptitude Guru</string>
    <string name="psycho">Psychometric</string>
    <string name="psychotest">Psychometric Test</string>
	<string name="psychoDemoQuestion">
		<b>Scenario</b>\n\n
		You are a Human Resources (HR) 
		Assistant working in the HR Department of a busy NHS Hospital Trust.
		The hospital is the Princess Aurora General in Saldringham City.\n\n Your 
		role is to carry out administrative tasks to support the HR 
		activities required in the Trust. You organise and support 
		recruitment, book training courses, provide secretarial support at 
		disciplinary investigations and keep personnel records for all 
		medical and non-medical staff up to date including pay and conditions 
		information.\n\n You report to one of two HR Managers who in turn report 
		to the HR Director. Your manager is called Fiona Potter.\n\n
		<b>Situation</b>\n\n
		It is three days after an interview process was held to appoint a new Consultant 
		Ophthalmologist for the hospital. This Consultant will be the most senior medical 
		person in the Ophthalmology (eye) department and in charge of three Senior 
		Registrars, two Registrars and Two House Officers – these are all junior doctors. 
		Consultant posts are rarely available as once people gain such a post they often 
		stay until they retire and there is lots of competition to gain a medical post at 
		the Trust, let alone a Consultant post with its associated security, status and 
		generous pay.\n\n
		Two internal; candidates plus an external candidate were interviews for the post and 
		the role was given to one of the internal candidates. The person appointed was 
		less experienced, in terms of their years as a Senior Registrar, than the other 
		two candidates but they were considered to be more ‘high-flying’, academically 
		gifted and to possess more impressive leadership skills than the other two.\n\n
		Mr Brian Bowler, the internal rejected candidate, has come to your office this 
		morning and is complaining bitterly about the decision. You were the one who wrote 
		the letters informing candidates of the decision. Mr Bowler is angry and feels unfairly 
		treated as he has more experience than Vijay Singh, the appointed candidate.\n\n
		Review the following responses A to D and indicate whether you believe the response to be 1 
		– the most effective response, 2 – the second most effective response, 3 – the third most 
		effective response or 4 – the least effective response. You may assign each rating only once.
		\n\n
		<b>Responses</b>\n\n
		<b>A</b> - Tell Mr Bowler that the process was fair and the hospital has to make sure that it 
		appoints the right person for the job, and not the one who has been around for the longest.\n\n
		<b>B</b> - Say that the interview board felt that Mr Singh was better academically and had 
		better leadership skills and that the final decision was not based on experience alone.\n\n
		<b>C</b> – Say to Mr Bowler that you can see why he is disappointed. State that the process 
		was stringently fair and that he could seek full details of the reason for the decision and 
		other developmental feedback from the interviews if he would like to.\n\n
		<b>D</b> – Offer him a cup of tea and say that you can understand why he is upset. Let him 
		have a bit of a moan to you and get it out of his system.
	</string>
	<string name="psychoCorrectAnswer">
	    <b>C</b> – The most effective response. You are emphasising with Mr Bowler but 
	    not supporting his negative view of the process. You are encouraging him to seek 
	    more information and feedback as to why he didn’t get the job which may help him 
	    develop and continue to contribute well to the department and the hospital.\n\n
	    <b>D</b> – The second most effective response. You are being sympathetic and 
	    friendly, although you are not helping him ‘move on’. Also there is a danger he 
	    may interpret your sympathy as support for his point of view.\n\n
	    <b>A</b> – The third most effective response. Although this is all perfectly true, 
	    it is a little insensitive and you are likely to alienate Mr Bowler and as he is 
	    still an employee at the hospital this may not be sensible.\n\n
	    <b>B</b> – The least effective response. Since you are only an assistant it is not 
	    your role to give such feedback to Mr Bowler, which may be counterproductive. You 
	    should also be encouraging him to seek feedback from the interviewers directly. 
	    Also, Mr Bowler needs to be given a fully-rounded picture of his performance at the 
	    interview and why the interviewers felt that they wouldn’t offer him the job on this 
	    occasion.
	</string>
</resources>